brother,
challenge of a real one here,
ó.
Jundiaí ninety days living on Chevette.
Oh caraca,
good,
good, good, good.
touch the ball,
Caraca, yes,
Yes, yes.
our bro,
Put the coin,
Put the currency.
to caraca,
hand
it was in my hand.
hand was playing wings.
happy,
Put the coin,
bro,
Put the currency here,
or, this way
No.
I lost the coin.
I stopped at a gas station here for boarding.
I'll even turn the camera over.
look at this,
bro,
not possible.
Bro,
got a flat tire on the chevos.
where is the other tire?
it's over there on the side of the workshop.
I'm glad you got it from the post
gave me a strength there,
traded it to me.
, that's great.
worth Giovani.
brother,
I have no real.
bro,
now i'm out of step.
cry will prevail
no will not.
it's bleeding there.
there's nothing to do.
palm bat.
asked,
there is 1 vacancy there.
How do you do it?
How does it work?
is interested.
doidão,
has 1 job position Ali.
wanted to know if for man you can too
OR is it just for women.
that is.
it's for women.
how did you get an equal percentage of work?
Are you doing it there?
talked to the guy downstairs,
with the Arab down there,
beyond the corner there.
Oh, that's how it is.
takes a test,
says there.
the text is for those in a hurry.
can't expect payment in thirty days
for you to eat today.
doidão,
has a value of.
daily rate of eighty reais the ticket value
and every customer who closes in the store
you earn 10reals for that customer.
O cool,
I'm making 1 registration,
now that you pay in the daily bag.
and then enjoying having 1 water bottle.
it's personal,
it won't be long before this promotion ends.
and then the most stylish man said he was going to come back,
bora do a free eye exam
my man we are going to take care of his health,
thank me
after
I managed to put two in there towards the store bro,
you say there
you who will?
will meet them with examination.
my dear,
Thanks,
Thanks Guy,
I hope I'm right there.
ok, thanks.
opportunity saw?
heart itself
mine from heaven,
what a crazy experience this is.
I never imagined that
forty hands,
look here
get forty,
i don't believe i
I worked until now.
I fixed the tire and ran out of zero money,
a real bread to be able to undertake old,
I will try
get something here.
Egypt,
that was day one.
until tomorrow.
The night was Young and the moon was
So we both decided to take a stroll.